Tom Hoskins collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Sound Recordings
  - AFC 2011/026: SR024, March 24, 26, 29, 1963; April 2, 1963, on one side of on 1 side of 1 sound tape reel (11 min., 10 sec.): analog, 15 ips, 1⁄2 track, 1 channel; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr024
    Original ID #24. On tape container: Reel 27 Silitch Fisher [Peter Silitch and Sandy Fisher]. "Dick" (mentioned on the recording) is Dick Spottswood. John starts by playing a 12-string guitar, then switches to a 6-string guitar. Silitch and Fisher recorded Hurt in sessions dated March 24, 26, 29 and April 2, 1963, in Washington, D.C.
    - When I lay my burden down
    - Blessed be the name
      Instrumental fragment.
    - Talking Casey Jones number two
      Two false starts.
    - [conversation]
  - AFC 2011/026: SR025, circa 1963-1966, on one side of on 1 side of 1 sound tape reel (15 min., 40 sec.): analog, 15 ips, 1⁄2 track, 1 channel; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr025
    Original ID #25. "SESS 2" "FILL II" / 28.
    - Talking Casey Jones number two
    - Sliding Delta
      Cuts off before song's conclusion.
    - Avalon blues
      Cut off at the beginning.
    - [conversation about playing Avalon blues]
      Conversation cuts out while in progress.
    - Waiting for you
    - I'm satisfied
    - Monday morning blues
      Cuts off before song's conclusion, when the tape runs out.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR026, March 24, 26, 29, 1963; April 2, 1963, on one side of on 1 side of 1 sound tape reel (16 min., 16 sec.): analog, 15 ips, 1⁄2 track, 1 channel; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr026
    Original ID #26. MJH 29 (written on reel). Dick Spottswood and Sandy Fisher are among the people who can be heard speaking on the recording.
    - Frankie and Johnnie
    - Trouble I've had it all my days
      First take completed; second take cut off before the conclusion.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR027, on one side of 1 sound tape reel (6 min., 33 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr027
    Original ID #27. MJH 30 (written on reel ). One man can be heard in the background, in conversation with John. More people arrive partway into the recording.
    - Joe Turner blues
    - Avalon blues
      Cut off before the conclusion.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR028, April 2, 1963, on one side of 1 sound tape reel (11 min., 14 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr028
    The box has "31" written on it. Original ID #28. This recording seems to be from the same session as SR26 and/or SR27. Voices can be heard in the background (including Sandy Fisher), sometimes in conversation with John. Continued on SR29, mid-song. See SR31 for a similar dub to this recording.
    - Coffee blues
    - Got the blues (Can't be satisfied)
    - Waiting for you [cut off]
  - AFC 2011/026: SR029, on one side of 1 sound tape reel (9 min., 41 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr029
    Continued from SR28, mid-song; continued on SR30. The box and reel have"32" written on each. Original ID #29.
    - Waiting for you [end]
    - Salty dog
    - Make me a pallet on the floor
    - [Walter tunes the guitar for John]
    - [conversation]
      The conversation is cut off before its conclusion.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR030, on one side of 1 sound tape reel (14 min., 15 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr030
    Original ID #30. Continued from SR29. On the tape container: "33."
    - Richland woman blues
    - Candy man
    - Louis Collins
    - Oh, Mary don't you weep
    - Do Lord, remember me
  - AFC 2011/026: SR031, March 24, 26, 29, 1963; April 2, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 30 min., 56 sec.; Side B: 32 min., 1 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr031
    Original ID #31. John Hurt Session dubs (6) Sandy Fisher and Peter Silitch present. See SR28 for notes; SR28 and SR31 are dubbed from the same source.
    - Side A
      - 00:55 Worried blues
      - 07:17 Joe Turner blues
      - 11:40 Cow hooking blues
      - 18:21 Avalon blues
      - 22:36 Coffee blues
      - 26:34 Got the blues (Can't be satisfied)
    - Side B
      - 00:20 [warming up]
      - 01:09 Spanish fandang
        First take. While the song is sometimes documented as "Spanish fandango," Hurt himself called it "Spanish fandang."
      - 03:17 Spanish fandang
      - 05:16 Casey Jones
      - 08:57 Sliding Delta
      - 11:03 Avalon blues
      - 13:18 Avalon blues
        Second take. Cut off before the conclusion.
      - 13:26 Waiting for you
        Cut off at the beginning; cuts out again at 15:26.
      - 15:57 I'm satisfied
      - 18:44 Monday morning blues
      - 21:00 Frankie and Johnnie
      - 26:06 Trouble, I've had it all my days
  - AFC 2011/026: SR032, April 2, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 31 min., 49 sec.; Side B: 31 min., 51 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr032
    Original ID #32. John Hurt Session dubs (5) / Silitch [Peter Silitch]. Possibly recorded at Sandy Fisher's house. Dick Spottswood was also present. John plays 12-string guitar.
    - Side A
      - 5:50 Candy man
      - 8:58 Sliding Delta
      - 14:11 Sliding Delta
      - 17:17 Candy man
      - 17:43 Candy man
      - 19:54 I'm satisfied
      - 22:33 Richland woman blues
      - 26:31 Monday morning blues
        Cut off at the beginning, and starts at the wrong speed.
      - 28:21 Monday morning blues
    - Side B
      - 01:22 Coffee blues
      - 04:45 Frankie and Johnnie
      - 09:08 Frankie and Johnnie
      - 13:17 All night long
      - 15:18 Monday morning blues
      - 21:01 When I lay my burden down
      - 25:34 Blessed be the name
        Fragment of an instrumental version of the song.
      - 26:00 Casey Jones
  - AFC 2011/026: SR033, December 15, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 32 min., 10 sec.; Side B: 32 min., 15 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips, 4 track; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr033
    Original ID #33. John Hurt and Dock Boggs workshop recorded by Folk Workshop, 1344 W. Jerome St., Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. From the beginning of the recording, a regular, high-pitched squeak or beep can be heard on the recording, possibly introduced by the recording device. Tape has drop out between 27:20-27:24. Mike Seeger may be heard speaking briefly on Side B.
    - Side A
      - 00:43 See See Rider
      - 05:17 Waiting for you
      - 08:32 [Question and answer segment]
      - 13:57 Let the mermaid flirt with me
      - 18:36 Candy man
      - 22:19 Casey Jones
      - 26:50 [Question and answer segment]
    - Side B
      - 00:29 Stagolee
      - 04:18: Rowan County Crew
        Dock Boggs, singing and playing banjo.
      - 12:14 [Question and answer segment]
      - 16:49 Old Joe's barroom
      - 21:44 Down South blues
      - 24:17 [Dock talks about discover the banjo and learning to play]
      - 26:50 Bright sunny South
      - 30:55 [Dock takes questions]
  - AFC 2011/026: SR034, 1 sound tape reel (5 min., 45 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr034
    Original ID #34. Recorded in front of a live audience. John announces the song as John Henry, spike driver.
    - 01:01 Spike driver blues
      Spoken introduction to the song.
    - 02:27 Spike driver blues
  - AFC 2011/026: SR035, 1 sound tape reel (31 min., 40 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr035
    Original ID #35. Recorded in front of a live audience. Talking Casey fades out at the end. John can be heard speaking with another man between songs.
    - 00:21 Richland woman blues
    - 04:56 Trouble I had all my days
    - 10:21 Chicken song
      One verse
    - 12:56 Coffee Blues (Every lovin’ spoonful)
    - 16:58 Monday mornin’ blues
    - 22:30 Frankie and Albert
    - 27:58 Talking Casey Jones
  - AFC 2011/026: SR036, January 27, 1965, 1 sound tape reel (28 min., 58 sec.): analog, 7 1/2, full track, mono; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr036
    Original ID #36. The year is unconfirmed. Recorded in front of a live audience. John can be heard speaking with another man between songs. The M.C. mentions the "Folklore Society" during the announcement of the intermission.
    - 00:26 Lonesome blues
    - 04:30 Let the mermaid flirt with me
    - 09:44 Candy man
    - 13:29 [intermission announced]
    - 13:58 My Creole belle
      Hurt announces the song as Creole belle.
    - 16:39 Make me a pallet on the floor
    - 20:40 Shake that thing
    - 23:02 Satisfied blues
    - 25:29 Salty dog
  - AFC 2011/026: SR037, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (30 min., 27 sec.): analog, 7 1/2, full track, mono; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr037
    Original ID #37. Recorded in front of a live audience.
    - 00:42 Here am I, oh Lord, send me
    - 5:54 Hot times in the old town tonight
    - 10:44 Nobody’s business
    - 15:45 Louis Collins
    - 21:46 Casey Jones
    - 26:55 Baby what's wrong with you
  - AFC 2011/026: SR038, February 14, 1964, 1 sound tape reel (47 min., 48 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips, mono; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr038
    Original ID #38. John Hurt live at Cafe Yana, reel 1. Drop-outs on "Do Lord, remember me." Alan Wilson (later with the group Canned Heat) played harmonica on the last four songs. SR038 and SR040a were recorded at the same time, although SR040a is the louder of the two. It is possible that they were made on recording devices positioned in separate places on or near the stage.
    - 00:49 Do Lord, remember me
      Hurt announces the song as Lord, remember me.
    - 06:24 When I lay my burden down
      Hurt announces the song as Since I've laid this burden down.
    - 12:22 C. C. Rider
    - 16:57 Worried blues
      Hurt announces the song as Worrisome blues.
    - 22:04 Monday morning blues
    - 27:41 My Creole belle
    - 31:39 Avalon blues
    - 35:46 Can’t be satisfied
      Hurt announces the song as Got the blues, can't be satisfied.
    - 39:16 Cow hooking blues
    - 43:48 Spike driver blues
      Hurt announces the song as Spike driver's moan (John Henry).
  - AFC 2011/026: SR039, February 14, 1964, 1 sound tape reel (47 min., 52 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips, 1/2 track; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr039
    Original ID #39. John Hurt. John Hurt live at Cafe Yana, reel 2. Alan Wilson played harmonica on the first two songs. SR039 and SR040b were recorded at the same time, although SR040b is the louder of the two. It is possible that they were made on recording devices positioned in separate places on or near the stage.
    - 00:19 Trouble, I've had it all my days
      Hurt announces the song as Trouble, I've had all my days.
    - 04:30 Sliding Delta
    - 09:17 Salty dog
    - 13:34 Casey Jones
    - 20:06 Nobody’s business
    - 25:53 Waiting for you
    - 33:15 Coffee blues
    - 38:07 Candy man
    - 42:37 Stagolee
  - AFC 2011/026: SR040, February 14, 1964, 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 47 min., 53 sec.; Side B: 44 min., 21 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr040
    Original ID #40. John Hurt live at Cafe Yana, reel 1, sets 1-3. See notes for SR038 and SR039. Side B (and possibly Side A) dubbed from other recordings (possibly SR038-SR039).
    - Side A
      - 00:49 Do Lord, remember me
      - 06:29 When I lay my burden down
      - 12:31 C. C. Rider
      - 17:08 Worried blues
      - 22:20 Monday morning blues
      - 28:00 My Creole belle
      - 31:42 Avalon blues
      - 35:53 Can’t be satisfied
      - 39:28 Cow hooking blues
      - 44:00 Spike driver blues
    - Side B
      - 00:26 Trouble, I've had it all my days
      - 04:39 Sliding Delta
      - 09:50 Salty dog
      - 13:54 Casey Jones
        The audio cuts out at 15:24.
      - 15:51 Casey Jones
        Fragment.
      - 22:29 Nobody’s business
      - 28:21 Waiting for you
      - 35:50 Coffee blues
      - 40:34 Candy man
  - AFC 2011/026: SR041, February 15, 1964, 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 30 min., 36 sec.; Side B: 31 min., 22 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr041
    Original ID #41. John Hurt live at Cafe Yana, reel 2, set 4. Saturday afternoon.
    - Side A
      - 00:45 Stagolee
      - 06:34 Joe Turner
      - 11:00 You are my sunshine
      - 15:08 Spanish fandang
        See note for SR31b.
      - 17:33 Frankie and Albert
      - 23:07 Make me a pallet on the floor
      - 27:51 Keep on knocking
    - Side B
      - 00:03 I been cryin' since you been gone
      - 02:11 Mary, don't you weep
      - 05:43 Sliding Delta
      - 10:44 Baby, what's wrong with you
      - 15:39 Funky butt
      - 18:16 Funky butt
        An unidentified man sings along.
      - 19:33 Stocktime
      - 20:17 Good morning Miss Carrie
      - 25:24 Chicken song
      - 26:03 Chicken song
      - 26:54 Spike driver blues
  - AFC 2011/026: SR042, possibly February 16, 1964, 1 sound tape reel (32 min., 16 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr042
    Original ID #42. Party, Sunday morning. Possible recorded on one channel only. Shrill, repetitive sound throughout the recording may have been introduced by the recording device. Instances of distortion occur as well. Feedback, print-through, or recording on a different channel mars the recording from 25:09 to the end.
    - 00:04 [unidentified]
      Instrumental; the beginning is cut off.
    - 01:47 What a friend we have in Jesus
      Hurt plays guitar but does not sing; those present pick up the singing later in the song.
    - 07:13 Louis Collins
    - 12:22 Worried blues
      Instrumental version; the beginning is cut off.
    - 15:38 [sound of people talking; the guitar and Hurt can be just barely heard]
    - 18:34 Worried blues
      An unidentified woman from the audience comments during the song.
    - 25:09 [distortion and other issues; see note]
  - AFC 2011/026: SR043, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (17 min., 8 sec.): analog, 15 ips; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr043
    Original ID #43. Some sort of vibration can be heard on the recording, which occurred during the recording process.
    - 00:03 Coffee blues
    - 04:03 [unidentified]
    - 07:38 Stagolee
      Hurt's spoken introduction to the song, followed by three false starts, then the complete song at 11:24.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR044, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (20 min., 36 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr044
    Original ID #44. Written on the reel: M54. Another man's voice can be heard on the recording, speaking with Hurt. Hurt uses a slide with his guitar on the song Pera Lee.
    - 00:13 Monday morning blues
      Two false starts, then the complete song.
    - 05:37 Pera Lee
      Hurt uses a slide with his guitar on the song Pera Lee.
    - 08:09 If you don't want me baby
    - 11:59 Payday
    - 15:26 Frankie and Albert
  - AFC 2011/026: SR045, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (19 min., 54 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr045
    Original ID #45. Written on the reel: M55. Another man's voice can be heard on the recording, speaking with Hurt. "Pete" is also present (this could be a number of people associated with Hurt).
    - 00:08 Bye and bye I will see Jesus [after one false start]
    - 03:20 My Creole belle
    - 03:53 [unidentified]
    - 04:56 I shall not be moved
    - 08:55 Trouble I've had it all my days
    - 08:59 Trouble I've had it all my days
    - 13:58 If you don't want me baby
    - 14:59 If you don't want me baby
  - AFC 2011/026: SR046, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (15 min., 7 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr046
    Original ID #46. Written on the reel: M56. Recorded before a live audience. Hurt uses a slide with his guitar on the song Pera Lee.
    - 00:16 Pera Lee
    - 02:59 Stagolee
    - 07:27 Candy man
    - 12:00 You are my sunshine
  - AFC 2011/026: SR047, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (13 min., 17 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr047
    Original ID #47. Written on the reel: M57. Recorded before a live audience.
    - 00:07 Good morning Miss Carrie
    - 02:44 Oh Mary don't you weep
    - 06:31 Payday
    - 10:22 Tender virgins
  - AFC 2011/026: SR048, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (11 min., 9 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr048
    Original ID #48. Written on the reel: M58. Recorded before a live audience. Mule Ridin' Blues (Hey, Bub Blues) begins at 10:24. Originally recorded by Big Bill Broonzy and released in 1956.
    - 00:14 Over in the Gloryland
    - 03:25 Got the blues (Can't be satisfied)
      Hurt announces the song as Got the blues that can't be satisfied.
    - 08:04 Stocktime/Mule Ridin' Blues (Hey, Bub Blues)
  - AFC 2011/026: SR049, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (18 min., 16 sec.): analog, 15 ips, stereo; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr049
    Original ID #49. Written on the reel: M59. Recorded before a live audience. Volume levels change with some frequency.
    - 00:10 Worried blues
    - 04:54 See See Rider
    - 08:56 Casey Jones
    - 14:31 [intermission announced]
    - 14:46 Camp meeting tonight on the old camp ground
      Hurt announces the song as Preaching tonight on the old camp ground.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR050, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (40 min., 16 sec.): analog, full track, mono; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr050
    Original ID #50. Feb 28th; Mostly NY. A female voice can be heard reciting numbers through the recording to 28:44, and then the recitation starts again at 37:47; it may have been recorded on a separate channel and thus playing back simultaneously. Dick Spottswood is present and speaks about 33:34 with the interviewer; someone named Ross is also present. A camera is also mentioned, so this may accompany a filmed segment for broadcast.
    - 00:01 Avalon blues
    - 02:17-21:02 [interview]
    - 21:14 My Creole belle
      Fragment; cut off.
    - 22:59 [interview continues]
    - 23:10 Hop joint
    - 24:26 [interview continues]
    - 25:06 Candy Man
    - 27:44 Got the blues (Can't be satisfied)
      The interviewer introduces the song as I've got The blues and can’t be satisfied.
    - 31:16 Trouble had all my days
    - 33:21 [interviewer talks about the song Candy man and speaks to Dick Spottswood and Ross]
    - 37:46 Candy man
      Three false starts and a version where the sound fades out precede the complete version.
    - 40:01 [interviewer says "bravo, thank you very much, finish"]
  - AFC 2011/026: SR051, March 25, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (15 min., 58 sec.): analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr051
    Original ID #51. From the accompanying documentation: John Hurt at home c2. Teaching Avalon. Fang [Tom Hoskins], guitar. Significant echoing effect introduced during the recording process, sometimes becoming very loud.
    - 01:48 Sliding Delta
    - 05:21 [conversation between Tom Hoskins and another man]
    - 05:44 Coffee blues
    - 08:27 Avalon blues
    - 09:24 Avalon blues
    - 12:20 Avalon blues
      Second take; one of the men sings along with Hurt.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR052, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (5 min., 49 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr052
    Original ID #52. John Hurt Live / Demonstration tape. Several men talking, with Hurt playing. Multiple takes of the song Payday, with some false starts. At one point Hurt uses a slide with his guitar when playing. Another guitarist plays as well; he speaks more than once but is unidentified.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR053, June 1965, 1 sound tape reel (33 min., 43 sec.): analog; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr053
    Original ID #53. Recorded before a live audience.
    - 00:20 Make me a pallet on the floor
    - 03:49 Good morning Miss Carrie
    - 06:23 Hot time in the old town tonight
    - 10:28 Waiting for you
    - 16:21 Candy man
    - 20:05 Long lonesome
    - 22:34 Salty dog
    - 25:35 Stagolee
    - 30:16 Avalon blues
      The song is cut off (incomplete).
  - AFC 2011/026: SR054, June 1965, 1 sound tape reel (29 min., 24 sec.): analog; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr054
    Original ID #54. Recorded before a live audience.
    - 00:16 Nearer my God to Thee
      Part of the tune is similar to "Blessed be the name."
    - 05:19 I'm satisfied
      Hurt announces the song as "Satisfied."
    - 09:10 Got the blues (Can't be satisfied)
      Hurt announces the song as "Satisfied" (a different song from the preceding song).
    - 12:35 Funky butt
    - 14:30 Corrina, Corrina
      Hurt announces the song as "Corrina."
    - 19:39 Baby what's wrong with you
      Volume fades in and out briefly when Hurt begins singing.
    - 24:10 Coffee blues
  - AFC 2011/026: SR055, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (45 min., 16 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips, 1/2 track, mono; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr055
    Original ID #55. Recorded live at The Ontario Place, in Adams Morgan, Washington, D.C.
    - 00:04 [male emcee introduces Hurt]
    - 01:55 I could walk that lonesome valley
    - 07:43 Do Lord remember me
    - 13:33 Trouble I've had it all my days
    - 19:37 Casey Jones
    - 24:37 Let the mermaid flirt with me
    - 31:40 Richland woman blues
    - 37:36 Make me a pallet on the floor
    - 41:46 Salty dog
  - AFC 2011/026: SR056, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (1 hr., 10 min., 59 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips, 1/2 track, mono; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr056
    Original ID #56. Recorded live at Recorded live at Ontario Place, in Adams Morgan, Washington, D.C.
    - 00:08 [male emcee introduces Hurt before the next set begins]
    - 03:16 When the saints go marching in
    - 08:11 I shall not be moved
    - 13:22 Chicken song
      Introduction and one verse.
    - 15:53 Candy man
    - 20:38 Louis Collins
    - 25:41 Hot time in the old town tonight
    - 28:38 Nobody's dirty business
    - 32:33 Avalon blues
    - 37:51 Sliding Delta
    - 42:54 Coffee blues
    - 47:57 See See Rider
    - 52:29 Joe Turner blues
      Hurt announces the song as "Old Joe Turner."
    - 56:37 Creole belle
    - 01:01:01 Spanish fandang
      Also known as "Spanish fandango."
    - 01:04:07 Talking Casey Jones
    - 01:09:18 [male emcee tells audience the performance is being recorded, talks about an upcoming performance by Skip James, and introduces Chuck Perdue]
  - AFC 2011/026: SR057, November 28, 1964; undated, 1 sound tape reel (1 hr., 32 min., 39 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips, 1/2 track, mono; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr057
    Original ID #57. Dubs from various sets; uncertain if all are from the same venue. All recordings except for the first (Canned heat) were recorded on November 28, 1964, at Ontario Place, in Adams Morgan, Washington, D.C.
    - Canned heat
      Possibly sung by Al Wilson, accompanied by guitar.
    - Welcome address
    - Frankie and Albert
    - Lonesome is I
    - Stagolee
    - Lonesome valley
    - Do Lord remember me
    - Baby please come home
    - [female emcee announces Hurt]
    - Lonesome valley
    - Do Lord remember me
    - Monday morning blues
    - Stagolee
      Spoken introduction to the song, followed by the song.
    - [male emcee introduces Hurt]
    - When the world's on fire
      Hurt announces the title as Rocks [sic] of ages.
    - Trouble I've had all my days
    - Let the mermaid flirt with me
  - AFC 2011/026: SR058, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 35 min., 22 sec.; Side B: 36 min., 46 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips, 1/2 track, mono; 10 in.
    Original ID #58. Recorded before a live audience.
    - Side A, afc2011026_sr058a
      - Waiting for you
      - Nobody's dirty business
      - Casey Jones
      - Louis Collins
      - You can't come in
        Hurt announces the song as Can't come in.
      - You are my sunshine
      - Make me a pallet on the floor
    - Side B, afc2011026_sr058b
      - Richland woman blues
      - Louis Collins
      - [male emcee announces Hurt]
      - Nobody's business
      - Let the mermaid flirt with me
      - Salty dog
      - Candy man
      - Worried blues
      - Coffee blues
  - AFC 2011/026: SR059, July 15, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (31 min., 15 sec.): analog, 15 ips; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr059
    Original ID #59. Recorded at the Coolidge Auditorium, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C. Dick Spottswood, Joseph (Joe) Hickerson, Robert Carneal, and John Howell. The latter two are recording engineers. Joe conducts the interview, which is interspersed between the songs. Continued on SR060.
    - Monday morning blues
    - Monday morning blues
    - Avalon blues
    - Joe Turner